mimeo.com 2019-04-24

# Privacy Policy - Mimeo.com

Mimeo.com, Inc. on behalf of itself and its subsidiary and affiliate companies (“Mimeo”, “We”, “Our”, “Us”) recognizes that your privacy and the protection of your personal information is important to you and is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the measures taken by us to protect your privacy in connection with your use of www.mimeo.com (our “Site”). This Privacy Statement discloses our collection, use and storage practices surrounding the personal information we collect from you when you visit our Site (regardless of where you visit it from). “Personal Information” is defined as the information such as your name, and email that can be used to identify you.

**This policy was last modified on May 24, 2018**

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY USING OUR SITE AND THE RELATED SERVICES PROVIDED BY MIMEO OR ITS DESIGNEES (THE “SERVICES”), YOU SIGNIFY YOUR AGREEMENT TO THIS POLICY.

Our Full Privacy Policy Is Given Below, But Here Are A Few Key Points: We will not sell, lease, or share your personal information with any other companies, except those who need it to help us serve you (e.g. providing your name, and address to our third party shipping agent and payment processor with whom we share your financial information to fulfill payment).

We will not spam you. For those few emails that we do send out, we always include a way for you to unsubscribe from any and all non-essential communications.

When you submit any form or upload any document to our Site, we use Secure Socket Layer Technology. Secure Socket Layer technology protects your information, using both server authentication and data encryption, ensuring that your data is safe, secure, and available only to registered users.

Once your documents have been uploaded, they are hosted in our secure server environment. We use firewalls and other advanced technologies to prevent interference or access from outside intruders.

In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

## Use of Personal Information.

We will use your personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:

Where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you.

Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.

Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.

Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data).

### Types of Data:

We may collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of personal data about you which we have grouped together as follows:

Identity Data includes first name, maiden name, last name, username or similar identifier, title, date of birth and gender.

Contact Data includes billing address, delivery address, custom return address, email address and telephone numbers.

Financial Data includes bank account and payment card details.

Transaction Data includes details about payments to and from you and other details of products and services you have purchased from us.

Technical Data includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this website.

Profile Data includes your username and password, purchases or orders made by you, your interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses.

Usage Data includes information about how you use our website, products and services.

Marketing and Communications Data includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.

We also collect, use and share Aggregated Data such as statistical or demographic data for any purpose. Aggregated Data may be derived from your personal data but is not considered personal data in law as this data does not directly or indirectly reveal your identity. For example, we may aggregate your Usage Data to calculate the percentage of users accessing a specific website feature. However, if we combine or connect Aggregated Data with your personal data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we treat the combined data as personal data which will be used in accordance with this privacy notice.

We do not collect any Special Categories of Personal Data about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data).

## What Information Is Collected By Mimeo.

In order to use the Services, you are required to provide us with an e-mail address and a unique password. In addition, when placing an order with our Site, you are required to provide personally identifying and other information such as your name, phone number, address, payment information (including credit card information), and shipping information (such as third party shipping addresses and shipping preferences).  We may use your Identity, Contact, Technical, Usage and Profile Data to form a view on what we think you may want or need, or what may be of interest to you. This is how we decide which products, services and offers may be relevant for you.

You will receive marketing communications from us if you have requested information from us or purchased goods or Services from us or if you provided us with your details when you registered for a promotion and you have not opted out of receiving that marketing.

Cookies and other tracking technologies: We and our partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.

### Analytics / Log Files:

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

### Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting:

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites.  Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.  If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising.  You will continue to receive generic ads.

We use Google AdSense to publish ads on this site.  When you view or click on an ad a cookie will be set to help better provide advertisements that may be of interest to you on this and other Web sites.   You may [opt-out of the use of this cookie by visiting Google’s Advertising and Privacy page](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads).

### Children’s Personally Identifiable Information:

The Services are neither directed toward children (under thirteen years of age), nor is it made available to children. We do not knowingly collect any personal information or accept orders from children.

### How The Information Collected Is Used:

The information collected from you when you place an order with our Site is used to contact you in the normal course of business (e.g. shipping documents and confirmation emails). Every time you place an order, we will send you a confirmation regarding your order status using the e-mail address that you have provided. You will know exactly when we have received your order, when the printing job is completed and even when we submit your documents to our partner carriers for shipping. We will provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. Once your order has been submitted to the carrier, all delivery service and tracking information is provided by the carrier. We also use your email to send you newsletters and promotions from our Site when you opt to receive this information from us. Your recipients may also receive emails if you opt to notify them of pending shipments Mimeo sends on your behalf.

We use non-personal information in aggregate form to build higher quality, more useful Services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our Customers and visitors, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the Site.

Mimeo does not share any personally identifiable information with third party parties for their promotional purposes; we will get your express opt-in consent before we share your personal data with any company outside of Mimeo or its subsidiary companies for marketing purposes. In addition, Mimeo will not use or share your personal information in a manner that differs from what is described in this Privacy Policy without your prior consent.

### Choice/Opt-Out:

We strive to provide you with choices regarding certain personal data uses, particularly around marketing and advertising.  Mimeo believes that all emails it sends to you after you sign up for an account are designed to help you best use the Services. The solicitations are limited in that they, among other things, will clearly indicate the originator of the e-mail and provide the customer with a method of “opting out” of receiving future communications of a similar nature. Non-essential communications, such as surveys or contests will not be shared with users who have opted out from our mailing list. Such individuals will only receive communications that are necessary for Mimeo to fulfill orders and provide customer service (e.g. confirmation email, delivery notification, etc). Please note that these communications are part of your Service and you generally cannot opt-out of them as a result.

To opt out of receiving non-essential communications, such as newsletters and promotions, users can click the “unsubscribe” link that is included at the bottom of any and all such communications.

## Purposes of Personal Data Use.

We have set out below, in a table format, a description of all the ways we plan to use your personal data, and which of the legal bases we rely on to do so. We have also identified what our legitimate interests are where appropriate.

Note that we may process your personal data for more than one lawful ground depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data. Please Contact us if you need details about the specific legal ground we are relying on to process your personal data where more than one ground has been set out in the table below.

**Purpose/Activity** | **Type of data** | **Lawful basis for processing including basis of legitimate interest**  
---|---|---  
To register you as a new customer | (a) Identity 

(b) Contact

| Performance of a contract with you  
To process and deliver your order including: 

(a) Manage payments, fees and charges

(b) Collect and recover money owed to us

| (a) Identity 

(b) Contact

(c) Financial

(d) Transaction

(e) Marketing and Communications

| (a) Performance of a contract with you 

(b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to recover debts due to us)  
  
To manage our relationship with you which will include: 

(a) Notifying you about changes to our terms or privacy policy

(b) Asking you to leave a review or take a survey

| (a) Identity 

(b) Contact

(c) Profile

(d) Marketing and Communications

| (a) Performance of a contract with you 

(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation

(c) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated and to study how customers use our products/services)  
  
To enable you to partake in a prize draw, competition or complete a survey | (a) Identity 

(b) Contact

(c) Profile

(d) Usage

(e) Marketing and Communications

| (a) Performance of a contract with you 

(b) Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them and grow our business)  
  
To administer and protect our business and this website (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data) | (a) Identity 

(b) Contact

(c) Technical

| (a) Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our business, provision of administration and IT services, network security, to prevent fraud and in the context of a business reorganization or group restructuring exercise) 

(b) Necessary to comply with a legal obligation  
  
To deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you | (a) Identity 

(b) Contact

(c) Profile

(d) Usage

(e) Marketing and Communications

(f) Technical

| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business and to inform our marketing strategy)  
To use data analytics to improve our website, products/services, marketing, customer relationships and experiences | (a) Technical 

(b) Usage

| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to define types of customers for our products and services, to keep our website updated and relevant, to develop our business and to inform our marketing strategy)  
To make suggestions and recommendations to you about goods or services that may be of interest to you | (a) Identity 

(b) Contact

(c) Technical

(d) Usage

(e) Profile

| Necessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our products/services and grow our business)  
  
## Change of Purpose.

We will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose. If you wish to get an explanation as to how the processing for the new purpose is compatible with the original purpose, please Contact us. If we need to use your personal data for an unrelated purpose, we will notify you and we will explain the legal basis which allows us to do so. Please note that we may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent, in compliance with the above rules, where this is required or permitted by law.

### When Your Information May Be Disclosed:

Mimeo reserves the right to disclose information or documents concerning or submitted by you as we reasonably feel is necessary to protect our systems or business, including but not limited to complying with a judicial order or with government agencies or law enforcement officials. Specifically, but without limitation, we reserve the right to disclose such information or documents when: you are in violation of our Terms and Conditions or other published guidelines; you partake (or are reasonably suspected of partaking) in any infringing or illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other court order; in response to court and governmental orders, civil subpoenas, discovery requests, and as otherwise required by law; as well as in response to allegations of infringement or illegality.

In the event of a sale, acquisition or merger of some, or all of Mimeo’s assets, your personal information would likely be a part of the transferred assets. In such an event, we shall notify you via a notice on our Site prior to the transfer, or by email, with your choices on how your information is to be used.

We require all third parties to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We do not allow our third-party service providers to use your personal data for their own purposes and only permit them to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

### Surveys, Sweepstakes And Contests:

Occasionally, Mimeo may conduct surveys in order to better deliver advertisements and content, and to better understand your needs relating to the Services. If you participate, we will request certain personal information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.  The requested information typically includes contact information such as name, email and shipping address and demographic information such as zip code. We will not share your survey information with any third party, except in aggregate form. In addition, if we sponsor a contest/sweepstakes or promotion in conjunction with a third party, we will post relevant privacy information at the point of registration for that specific contest/sweepstakes or promotion so you can determine whether you wish to participate. Mimeo will handle personal information it receives as a result of a joint contest/sweepstakes or promotion or where Mimeo is the sole sponsor in accordance with this privacy policy.

### Referral:

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our website, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the website. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [customercare@mimeo.com](mailto:customercare@mimeo.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

### Testimonial Disclosure:

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements.  With your written consent we may post your testimonial along with your name.

### How You May Access & Update Your Information:

Upon request we will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information.  If you would like to change, update or delete your personal information in our databases, you may do so through your Account Profile, or by contacting our customer care team. We will make reasonable efforts to comply with your request. We shall respond to your inquiry within 30 days of receiving it. Keep in mind, however, that there will be residual information that will remain within Mimeo databases, access logs, and other records, which may or may not contain inaccurate or outdated personal information. The residual information will not be used for commercial purposes; however Mimeo reserves the right, from time to time, to re-contact former users of the Services for the purpose of informing them of changes in our service or hours of service. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [customercare@mimeo.com](mailto:customercare@mimeo.com).

## Data Security.

### How Is My Information Protected?

We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorized way, altered or disclosed. Mimeo uses reasonable security an industry-standard security technology called Secure Socket Layer (SSL Encryption), a protocol developed by Netscape, for the secure transmission of sensitive information over the Internet. SSL works by using a private key to encrypt data that are transmitted over the SSL connection. Current versions of Google, Chrome, Netscape Navigator, Internet Explorer and America Online browsers support SSL, as do other browsers, and our Site uses SSL encryption when you transmit sensitive information, such as credit card numbers. Your document is uploaded to us using the same encryption settings your browser uses when connecting to our Site. Web pages that require an SSL connection generally start with “https” instead of “http”, although some pages and frames within pages may be encrypted even without the https address. Your browser’s help files can show you how to verify whether a particular page utilizes SSL.

In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.

We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.

### Updates To This Privacy Policy:

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last modified” date at the top of the Privacy Policy. If Mimeo changes any of its policies that affect users’ personal information, the changes will be posted in this document, and prominently on the public and private web sites (www.mimeo.com and my.mimeo.com) for 30 consecutive business days prior to the implementation of those changes. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective.  We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates.

### Terms & Conditions:

Please also visit our Terms & Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Site.

### Third Party Links:

The Mimeo web site may contain links to other Internet web sites, including co-branded or other affiliated sites, which may or may not be owned or operated by Mimeo. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. This Privacy Policy only covers our Site and does not cover any other website. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. We strongly encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of those sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).

### Social Media Widgets:

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

## Data Retention.

### How Long Will You Keep and Use My Personal Data?

We keep basic information about our customers (including Contact, Identity, Financial and Transaction Data) years after they cease being customers as reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations (including law enforcement requests), meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, maintain security, prevent fraud and abuse, fulfill your request to “unsubscribe” from further messages from us.

In some circumstances you can ask us to delete your data: see Request erasure, under Your Legal Rights below for further information.

In some circumstances we may anonymize your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for research or statistical purposes in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you.

### Your Legal Rights:

Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data. If you wish to exercise any of your rights, please contact us: [dpo@mimeo.com](mailto:dpo@mimeo.com).

## Glossary.

Lawful Basis – Legitimate Interest means the interest of our business in conducting and managing our business to enable us to give you the best service/product and the best and most secure experience. We make sure we consider and balance any potential impact on you (both positive and negative) and your rights before we process your personal data for our legitimate interests. We do not use your personal data for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law). You can obtain further information about how we assess our legitimate interests against any potential impact on you in respect of specific activities by contacting us at [dpo@mimeo.com](mailto:dpo@mimeo.com).

### Contacting Us:

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, the Service, or Mimeo.com, please e-mail us at [dpo@mimeo.com](mailto:dpo@mimeo.com). If at any time you do not agree to this Policy, please call 1-800-Go-Mimeo to cancel your account or write to us at the address below:

We have appointed a data protection officer (DPO) who is responsible for overseeing questions in relation to this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this privacy notice, including any requests to exercise your legal rights, please contact the DPO using the details set out below.

**CONTACT DETAILS**

Our full details are:

Mimeo.com, Inc.  
Attn: Data Protection Officer  
3 Park Avenue. 22nd FL  
New York, NY 10016  
212-847-3009
